<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AquaQuality</string>
    <string name="label_email">Email</string>
    <string name="label_password">Password</string>
    <string name="label_repeat_password">Repeat Password</string>
    <string name="label_login">Login</string>
    <string name="label_create_account">Create Account</string>
    <string name="label_google_signin">Sign-in with Google</string>
    <string name="label_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="credits">© 2023 IT-39 DHVSU</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back Button</string>
    <string name="get_started">Get Started</string>
    <string name="home_press_plus_message">To get started, press the plus( + ) button on the lower right side of the screen.</string>
    <string name="parameter_temperature">%s℃</string>
    <string name="parameter_pH">%s</string>
    <string name="parameter_turbidity">%s NTU</string>
    <string name="label_temperature">Temperature</string>
    <string name="label_pH">pH</string>
    <string name="label_turbidity">Turbidity</string>
    <string name="label_wUnit_temperature">Temperature (℃)</string>
    <string name="label_wUnit_pH">pH</string>
    <string name="label_wUnit_turbidity">Turbidity (NTU)</string>
    <string name="label_save_changes">Save Changes</string>
    <string name="title_app_settings">App Settings</string>
    <string name="label_min_temp">Minimum (℃)</string>
    <string name="label_max_temp">Maximum (℃)</string>
    <string name="title_temperature_threshold">Temperature Threshold</string>
    <string name="title_ph_level_threshold">pH Level Threshold</string>
    <string name="label_min_ph">Minimum (pH)</string>
    <string name="label_max_ph">Maximum (pH)</string>
    <string name="title_turbidity_threshold">Turbidity Threshold</string>
    <string name="label_min_turb">Minimum (NTU)</string>
    <string name="label_max_turb">Maximum (NTU)</string>
    <string name="value_rec_min_temp">28</string>
    <string name="value_rec_max_temp">32</string>
    <string name="value_rec_min_ph">6.5</string>
    <string name="value_rec_max_ph">8.5</string>
    <string name="value_rec_min_turb">0</string>
    <string name="value_rec_max_turb">180</string>
    <string name="label_user_profile_photo_placeholder">User Profile Photo Placeholder</string>
    <string name="desc_toggle_password_visibility">Toggle password visibility</string>
    <string name="label_name">Name</string>
    <string name="message_no_device">Connect a AquaQuality Monitoring Device to see current water quality parameter measurements</string>
    <string name="message_no_data">There is no data to display.</string>
    <string name="label_add_device">Add Device</string>
    <string name="web_client_id">645304250386-r97t99t2fdnuu11ogq91pgn05n6poet2.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
    <string name="desc_sign_in_with_google">Sign-in with Google</string>
    <string name="label_edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="label_delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="warning_password_format">The password must be at least 8 characters long and at least one uppercase letter, one lowercase letter, and one number</string>
    <string name="warning_incorrect_repeat_password">Passwords do not match.</string>
    <string name="warning_invalid_email">Invalid email address.</string>
    <string name="notif_channel_name">AqNotif</string>
    <string name="notif_channel_desc">AquaQuality warning notifications</string>
    <string name="label_water_quality_guide">Water Quality Guide</string>
    <string name="statement_optimal_temp">The optimal water temperature range for aquaculture is 28℃ - 32℃.</string>
    <string name="temp_paragraph_1">\t\tFish are cold-blooded animals, but their body temperature changes depending on the temperature of the water around them. This affects their metabolism and physiology, which can impact their health and productivity.</string>
    <string name="temp_paragraph_2">\t\tWhen the water temperature increases, the fish\'s metabolism and respiration rate also increase. This means that they need more oxygen to survive. Moreover, the amount of oxygen that can dissolve in water decreases as the temperature increases. This can lead to oxygen levels in the water becoming too low for the fish to survive.</string>
    <string name="temp_paragraph_3">\t\tLow temperature can reduce the feed intake and growth rate of catfish. Catfish need a warm water temperature of about 26°C to 32°C to digest their food well and grow fast. Low temperature can also change the water quality in the fishponds. Low temperature can reduce the oxygen level and increase the ammonia level in the water. Oxygen is needed by catfish to breathe and by bacteria to break down wastes.</string>
    <string name="statement_optimal_ph">The desirable pH level range for freshwater fishes in the Philippines is 6.5 – 8.5.</string>
    <string name="ph_paragraph_1">\t\tThe pH of water is a measure of how acidic or alkaline it is. Most fish prefer water with a pH between 6.5 and 9.0. Water with a pH that is too low or too high can harm fishes. When the pH of water is too low, it can damage the fish\'s gills and make it difficult for them to breathe. It can also make the water more toxic to fish. When the pH of water is too high, it can make the water less oxygenated, which can suffocate the fish. It can also make the water more alkaline, which can damage the fish\'s skin and eyes.</string>
    <string name="ph_paragraph_2">\t\tThe pH of water can be affected by a number of factors, including the type of rocks and soil in the water, the amount of sunlight the water receives, and the type of plants and animals that live in the water.</string>
    <string name="statement_optimal_turb">The recommended water turbidity range for fishponds is 0 – 180 NTU.</string>
    <string name="turb_paragraph_1">\t\tIf the turbidity of the water in the pond is too high, it can block the sunlight from reaching the plants and algae in the water. These plants and algae are important for producing oxygen and food for the fish. Without enough sunlight, they cannot grow well and may die. This reduces the oxygen level and the food supply for the fish.</string>
    <string name="turb_paragraph_2">\t\tHigh water turbidity can also carry harmful substances, such as sediments, chemicals, bacteria, and parasites, that can damage the gills, skin, eyes, and internal organs of the fish. These substances can also reduce the quality of the water and make it more acidic or alkaline. This can stress the fish and make them more vulnerable to diseases and infections.</string>
    <string name="label_dark_theme">Dark Theme</string>


    <string name="highTempTreatment1">Increase the flow of water by using pumps, aerators, or fountains. This method can also help in lowering the water temperature by blending it with cooler water that comes from deeper layers or other sources.</string>
    <string name="highTempConsequences1">When the water temperature increases, the fish\'s metabolism and respiration rate also increase. This means that they need more oxygen to survive.</string>
    <string name="highTempConsequences2">Moreover, the amount of oxygen that can dissolve in water decreases as the temperature increases. This can lead to oxygen levels in the water becoming too low for the fish to survive.</string>
    <string name="high_temp_headline">The water temperature of one of the fishponds has exceeded the recommended range.</string>
    <string name="low_temp_headline">The temperature of one of the fishponds is below the recommended range.</string>
    <string name="lowTempTreatments1">Try to reduce the water exchange or circulation the water in the pond. This can help retain the heat in the water and prevent it from being mixed with colder water from outside sources</string>
    <string name="lowTempTreatments2">Increase the feeding rate or use high-protein feeds. Feeding can increase the metabolic rate and heat production of the fish, as well as their immunity and growth. However, feeding should be done carefully and according to the appetite of the fish, as overfeeding can cause water quality problems.</string>
    <string name="lowTempConsequence1">Low temperature can reduce the feed intake and growth rate of catfish. Catfish need a warm water temperature of about 26°C to 32°C to digest their food well and grow fast.</string>
    <string name="lowTempConsequence2">Low temperature can also change the water quality in the fishponds. Low temperature can reduce the oxygen level and increase the ammonia level in the water. Oxygen is needed by catfish to breathe and by bacteria to break down wastes.</string>
    <string name="highPhTreatments1">For fishponds, it is recommended to change the water in the pond to normalize its pH level.</string>
    <string name="highPhConsequences1">When the pH of water is too high, it can make the water less oxygenated, which can suffocate the fish.</string>
    <string name="highPhConsequences2">It can also make the water more alkaline, which can damage the fish\'s skin and eyes.</string>
    <string name="lowPhTreatments1">For fishponds, it is recommended to change the water in the pond to normalize its pH level.</string>
    <string name="lowPhConsequences1">When the pH of water is too low, it can damage the fish\'s gills and make it difficult for them to breathe.</string>
    <string name="lowPhConsequences2">It can also make the water more toxic to fish.</string>
    <string name="high_ph_headline">The pH level of one of the fishponds has exceeded the recommended range.</string>
    <string name="low_ph_headline">The pH level of one of the fishponds is below the recommended range.</string>
    <string name="highTurbTreatments1">For fishponds, it is recommended to change the water in the pond to clear the excess suspend solids in the water.</string>
    <string name="highTurbConsequences1">If the turbidity of the water in the pond is too high, it can block the sunlight from reaching the plants and algae in the water. These plants and algae are important for producing oxygen and food for the fish. Without enough sunlight, they cannot grow well and may die. This reduces the oxygen level and the food supply for the fish.</string>
    <string name="highTurbConsequences2">High water turbidity can also carry harmful substances, such as sediments, chemicals, bacteria, and parasites, that can damage the gills, skin, eyes, and internal organs of the fish. These substances can also reduce the quality of the water and make it more acidic or alkaline. This can stress the fish and make them more vulnerable to diseases and infections.</string>
    <string name="lowTurbTreatments1">Low water turbidity does not require any treatment.</string>
    <string name="lowTurbConsequences1">There are no known negative consequence for low water turbidity.</string>
    <string name="high_turb_headline">The turbidity of one of the fishponds has exceeded the recommended range.</string>
    <string name="low_turb_headline">The turbidity of one of the fishponds is below the recommended range.</string>
    <string name="label_language">Language</string>
    <string name="message_connect_to_view">Connect a AquaQuality Monitoring Device to see water quality parameter measurements</string>
    <string name="label_time">Time</string>
    <string name="label_recommended_value">Recommended value: %s</string>
    <string name="message_enter_fishpond_name">Enter fishpond name</string>
    <string name="message_description_optional">Description(optional)</string>
    <string name="message_delete_confirrm">Are you sure you want to delete %s and all its related information? This action cannot be undone.</string>
    <string name="message_disconnect">Are you sure you want to disconnect from %s? Real-time monitoring will be unavailable unless a device is connected.</string>
    <string name="label_description">Description</string>
    <string name="label_home">Home</string>
    <string name="label_guide">Water Quality Guide</string>
    <string name="label_settings">App Settings</string>
    <string name="label_account">User Account</string>
    <string name="report_item_temp">At %s, with a value of %.2f %s</string>
    <string name="report_normal_temp">The water %s in the fishpond was normal all throughout this day.</string>
    <string name="report_temp_header">\tThe fishpond’s water %s was found to be anomalous during the following times:</string>
</resources>
